{
	"name": "Unit 1",
	"type": "writing",
	"questions": [
		{
			"question_text": "książka",
			"correct_answer": "book"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "kalkulator",
			"correct_answer": "calculator"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "kredka",
			"correct_answer": "crayon"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "zeszyt",
			"correct_answer": "notebook"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "długopis",
			"correct_answer": "pen"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "ołówek",
			"correct_answer": "pencil"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "piórnik",
			"correct_answer": "pencil case"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "gumka",
			"correct_answer": "rubber"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "linijka",
			"correct_answer": "ruler"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "plecak szkolny",
			"correct_answer": "school bag"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "nożyczki",
			"correct_answer": "scissors"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "temperówka",
			"correct_answer": "sharpener"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "sztuka",
			"correct_answer": "art"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "język angielski",
			"correct_answer": "English"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "język niemiecki",
			"correct_answer": "German"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "historia",
			"correct_answer": "history"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "matematyka",
			"correct_answer": "maths"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "muzyka",
			"correct_answer": "music"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "wychowanie fizyczne (WF)",
			"correct_answer": "PE"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "przyroda",
			"correct_answer": "science"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "język hiszpański",
			"correct_answer": "Spanish"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "technika",
			"correct_answer": "technology"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "czerwony",
			"correct_answer": "red"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "pomarańczowy",
			"correct_answer": "orange"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "żółty",
			"correct_answer": "yellow"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "jasnozielony",
			"correct_answer": "light green"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "ciemnozielony",
			"correct_answer": "dark green"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "jasnoniebieski",
			"correct_answer": "light blue"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "ciemnoniebieski",
			"correct_answer": "dark blue"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "fioletowy",
			"correct_answer": "purple"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "czarny",
			"correct_answer": "black"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "biały",
			"correct_answer": "white"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "szary",
			"correct_answer": "grey"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "brązowy",
			"correct_answer": "brown"
		},
		{
			"question_text": "różowy",
			"correct_answer": "pink"
		}
	]
}
